<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="answer1">
        <item>You were honest, but it impacted your grade.</item>
        <item>The teacher pushed the test date a few days back and your whole class appreciated your action.</item>
        <item>Did you really think, that this would work?</item>
        <item>You try to convince him and it works.</item>
        <item>You did nothing useful.</item>
        <item>You successfully ignored her.</item>
        <item>You successfully ignored them.</item>
        <item>You wrote the essay.</item>
        <item>You get even more stressed, but at least you learned a little bit.</item>
        <item>The teacher explained it again for you and now you understand it better.</item>
        <item>You took some money, but at least for now, nobody noticed.</item>
        <item>You let it burn and the teacher notices. Now the whole class is on fire and you have a big problem.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="answer2">
        <item>You did it, but your classmates don\'t like that you did that.</item>
        <item>You failed.</item>
        <item>You got a entry in the class register.</item>
        <item>He gets even more angry.</item>
        <item>You talk to your friends and classmates and that\'s it.</item>
        <item>You helped her and you got to know each other a little better.</item>
        <item>You talked to them and got to know each other better.</item>
        <item>Nobody wanted to write it for you, so you haven\'t done it.</item>
        <item>You were so stressed after you tried to learn and repeat everything, that you got so confused that you failed the test.</item>
        <item>You understood him better than the teacher could ever explain.</item>
        <item>You left the wallet there.</item>
        <item>You failed horribly and the fire got even bigger. Now the teacher notices and the whole class is on fire and you have a big problem.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="answer3">
        <item>The teacher noticed and you got a bad grade.</item>
        <item>You tried to copy it from your neighbour, but he did fail, so you did too.</item>
        <item>It didn\'t work.</item>
        <item>Your neighbor even helps you to answer his question and it works.</item>
        <item>You have a nice time, but you completely ignored all of your friends.</item>
        <item>She refused.</item>
        <item>They did what you asked them to do.</item>
        <item>You hired a ghostwriter, but it was expensive.</item>
        <item>You calmed down, therefore it was easier for you to concentrate and you got a better grade.</item>
        <item>You did nothing.</item>
        <item>You got a lot of money, but a classmate noticed and now you are in big trouble.</item>
        <item>He easily extinguish it.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="answer4">
        <item>You said, that your dog had eaten your homework, and your teacher didn\'t trust you.</item>
        <item>You got what you would expect.</item>
        <item>You successfully committed suicide.</item>
        <item>He calms down, but still gives you a bad grade.</item>
        <item>You have done your homework, congrats.</item>
        <item>You found somebody.</item>
        <item>Now you got new neighbours.</item>
        <item>You successfully did nothing.</item>
        <item>You went home, but when you needed to write the test again, you failed.</item>
        <item>You tried but you failed.</item>
        <item>You gave it to the teacher, but you never received finder money.</item>
        <item>The fire alarm goes off and the teacher extinguish the fire. But now all students are out of the building.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="defaultAnswers">
        <item>You did what you wanted to do.</item>
        <item>You succeed.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>