<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="choice1">
        <item>Be honest!</item>
        <item>Convince the teacher to write the test next lesson.</item>
        <item>Start to cry and say that you are not this person. Your only hope is that he believes you.</item>
        <item>Tell him that you calculated something important and can\'t answer his question</item>
        <item>Just get bored.</item>
        <item>Ignore her.</item>
        <item>Ignore them.</item>
        <item>Write it by yourself.</item>
        <item>Ask your classmates some questions about the test and let them ask you some questions too.</item>
        <item>Ask the teacher if he could explain it again for you.</item>
        <item>Take some money and leave it there.</item>
        <item>Just let it burn.</item>
        <item>You pick yes.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="choice2">
        <item>Go to the toilet and try to solve it.</item>
        <item>Stay quiet and try to solve the task.</item>
        <item>Stay quiet and get an entry in the class register.</item>
        <item>Say nothing and risk that the teacher will give you a bad grade.</item>
        <item>Talk to someone.</item>
        <item>Try to help her.</item>
        <item>Talk with them.</item>
        <item>Ask somebody if he could write it for you.</item>
        <item>Try to learn and repeat everything that you need to know for your test.</item>
        <item>Ask your neighbor if he could help you.</item>
        <item>Leave the wallet there.</item>
        <item>Try to extinguish it.</item>
        <item>You pick no.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="choice3">
        <item>Try to copy the homework from someone else.</item>
        <item>Stay quiet and try to copy the answers from someone else.</item>
        <item>Try to argue with him.</item>
        <item>Put the calculator away and try to answer the question.</item>
        <item>Just stare into your smartphone.</item>
        <item>Ask for money before you help her.</item>
        <item>Ask them if they could stop that.</item>
        <item>Get a ghostwriter to write it for you.</item>
        <item>Try to calm down.</item>
        <item>Do nothing.</item>
        <item>Take all the money and leave it.</item>
        <item>Tell the teacher.</item>
        <item>You try to get the answer from your neighbor.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="choice4">
        <item>Tell the teacher a lie.</item>
        <item>Leave a blank letter.</item>
        <item>Commit suicide.</item>
        <item>Say you are really sorry and put the calculator in your backpack.</item>
        <item>Do your homework.</item>
        <item>Ask someone else if he could help her.</item>
        <item>Get to another seat.</item>
        <item>Just don\'t write it.</item>
        <item>Tell the teacher that you don\'t fell so good and need to go home.</item>
        <item>Try harder to understand it.</item>
        <item>Give the wallet to your teacher.</item>
        <item>Press the flue and do nothing.</item>
        <item>You leave the exercise unfinished.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>